Vedran Arnautovic

Lead Product Designer, Zendesk

527 Brunswick Street Fitzroy North VIC 3068

phone 0434 490 076 web vedran.io email hello@vedran.io twitter @vedranio

I'm a user centred designer equally comfortable in the minutiae of pixel detail and ambiguity of early product discovery. I focus on design systems, UX design, usability, interaction design and user research. I can code (a little).

Experience

Zendesk

Jul 2018 - present

Zendesk

Nov 2017 - Jul 2018

SEEK

Jan 2014 - Nov 2017

Lead Product Designer

- Leading design for Zendesk admin experience
- Working on Zendesk's design system

Senior Product Designer

- Conducted a large scale research project looking into needs of Zendesk administrators
- Initiated design of Zendesk's new Admin Centre

Senior UX Designer

My work was a mixture of tactical projects where I closely worked with small agile teams, and strategic efforts, working closely with senior leaders to define the future of SEEK's products.

Freelance Lead UX designer

Sep 2016 - Oct 2017

Gymsales

Led all aspects of design for Gymsales.

Rubicon

Ran a week long design sprint for Rubicon's clients.

Kolektiv

Coached Kolektiv's team on lean UX practices.

SMS

Sep 2010 - Jan 2014

Consultant (UX designer and BA)

- UX Designer and BA (NAB)
- Interface Designer and BA (BP)

Internally, I was appointed the Customer Experience (CX) lead for Victoria kickstarting the development of our CX capability.

Leica

Feb 2009 – Sep 2010 Melbourne

System Design Engineer & BA

Upon returning to Melbourne, I worked with Leica's software team to define design improvements based on my field research.

Leica

Feb 2007 - Feb 2009 London

System Design Engineer

A career shaping opportunity allowed me to spend two years researching how our clients and support teams interacted with our instruments, and to use those findings to design better solutions for them.

Vision BioSystems

Jan 2004 - Feb 2007

Software Engineer

I started out very technical, developing software for medical devices. Working in an organisation with no designers created a window of opportunity to start designing and show initiative to test software with users.

Education

Univ. of Melbourne

1999 - 2004

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

Bachelor's degree, Mechatronics

Tools

Sketch, Adobe CC, Marvel, Invision, Axure, Morae, Principle, Framer.js, CSS, HTML, Javascript, Github

+ anything else I need to learn.